

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Details
Shenzhen, China
8615321271919
332518418@qq.com

Links

Portfolio

Github

LinkedIn

Instagram

Skills

JavaScript

Redux

React Router

React

Typescript

Node.js

Next.js

GraphQl

Vue.js

Tailwind CSS

Styled Components

jQuery

Git

Languages

Mandarin

English

### **Profile**

I am a web developer with 7 years' experience. Knowledgeable in user interface, testing, maintenance of web systems and debugging processes. Good at solving problems related to web for companies and customers with high efficiency. Proficient in an assortment of technologies, including JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Typescript, Node.js, React, Redux, Next.js, Axios, etc. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

## **Employment History**

#### Web Developer, Yonghui Supermarket Corporation, Beijing

OCTOBER 2018 - APRIL 2022

- Wrote modern, performant, maintainable code for in-house admin dashboard projects, including monitoring system, shop devices management system, marketing campaign planning system, etc
- Worked well independently and within a team setting using different languages, frameworks, and libraries such as JavaScript, React, Redux, TypeScript, Styled Components, Ant Design, Vue.js and Vuex
- Communicated with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, product managers on a regular basis
- Provided effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications

#### Web Developer, Sao Tianxia, Beijing

UNE 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2018

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed and maintained web applications, mostly mobile oriented user interfaces
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and systems requirements
- Worked with Vue.js, Vuex, CSS3, Sass, ElementUI, Webpack, Gulp to build web
  pages on different sizes of mobile phones
- Followed policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times

#### Web Developer, Zhu Baijia, Beijing

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JUNE 2016

- Developed and maintained code primarily using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and iQuery
- Worked at an independent level, while also serving as an effective and enthusiastic collaborator
- Implemented and updated application modules under the direction of Senior Software Developers

# **Personal Projects**

#### **Headless CMS Blog**

June 2022

A responsive blog website with featured and recent posts, categories. full markdown articles, author information, comments, etc. Using React, Next.js, GraphQl, Tailwindcss

## React Simple Realization @17.0.2

April 2022 - May 2022

A study notebook to better understand the mechanism of react(precisely @17.0.2), including hooks api, batch updates, synthetic events, dom-diff, etc

## **Education**

Master Degree, Internation Relations, China Foreign Affairs University